justfreshkicks.com 2016-11-30

# Privacy Policy - JustFreshKicks

At JustFreshKicks.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by JustFreshKicks.com and how it is used. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to provide advertisements and links that appear on JustFreshKicks.com, which are sent directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by these third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
  
JustFreshKicks.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. JustFreshKicks.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, JustFreshKicks.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  
   
**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
JustFreshKicks.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Cookies are files with small amounts of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our site.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Security**  
The security of your Personal Information is very important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on JustFreshKicks.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to JustFreshKicks.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Links To Other Sites**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. JustFreshKicks.com has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party sites or services.

**Third Party Disclosure**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Privacy Policy / Terms and Conditions**  
We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at [www.JustFreshKicks.com](http://www.justfreshkix.com/).

**Changes To This Privacy Policy  
**JustFreshKicks.com may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at Info@JustFreshKix.com.
